disruptiveadvertising.com 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Disruptive Advertising

Disruptive Advertising Privacy Policy

At Disruptive Advertising, we respect and protect the privacy of our clients and users who visit our websites. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information for Disruptive Advertising services, including the advertising services, promotions, informational mailings, and other offers we provide. By using any services provided by Disruptive Advertising, Inc. (“Disruptive Advertising”), you indicate that you agree to the collection and use of your information by Disruptive Advertising as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, please note that in the event that you provide information to us and then choose not to use our services, the information you provide to us will still be handled as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

1\. Why We Collect Information  
First and foremost, Disruptive Advertising collects information to improve the services we provide and to present you with information and services that may interest you. We also use your information to measure our success and performance. For example, aggregate information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate our websites.

2\. Personal Information Collection and Communication  
Disruptive Advertising is the sole owner of information collected on this website. Any personal information collected by us is provided by you strictly on a voluntary basis. You may submit your personal information in a number of ways, depending on the Disruptive Advertising service you are using and your choices while using our services. For example, if you choose to run an advertising campaign through Disruptive Advertising, during registration we may ask you for, and you may choose to give to us, information such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, credit card information, or other personal information necessary to complete a transaction or provide services to you. We use this information, such as your email address, to send you information and notices about the services you have requested and are receiving from us (“Service Messages”), as well as information about our company, client campaigns, and our other products and services which may interest you (together, “Marketing Messages”). The ability to send you Service Messages is an important part of our ability to serve you, and they will continue for as long as you continue to receive our services. Marketing Messages are optional. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive Marketing Messages. Whether you receive services from us or not, we provide you the opportunity to opt out of having your personally identifiable information used for Marketing Messages by emailing unsubscribe@DisruptiveAdvertising.com at any time. In any such email, please provide us your name, email address, phone number, physical address, business name, and domain with “Marketing Messages Opt-Out” in the subject line, so that we can properly identify you and process your opt-out request. Please note that a reasonable period of time will be required to process your request after Disruptive Advertising receives it, and you may continue to receive Marketing Messages during the processing period.  
You may submit your credit card information online or over the phone when you sign up for our services. We process payments through Litle& Co. This company and other companies we may do business with in order to provide the services you request from us will not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any purpose other than billing for our services.

3\. Personal Information You Provide  
As stated above, unless you voluntarily provide personal information for a specific purpose, we do not collect personal information from you. We will never combine any personal information about a user of our site with any aggregate information we collect about that user, whether collected on our site or our Advertising Service. If you choose to provide personal information during registration or when using our services, we use your personal information to provide you with particular product or services that you request. If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, or delete it by emailing our Customer Support at support@DisruptiveAdvertising.com or by calling 1-877-956-7510.

4\. Limited Third-Party Use of Personal Information  
In the event that you have been referred to our services by or through an Disruptive Advertising partnership promotion (such as through the Yahoo! Small Business Marketing Dashboard or other Yahoo!-sponsored promotion or site), such that our Promotional Partner (as defined in the Terms and Conditions you agreed to when obtaining our services) is a beneficiary of our relationship with you, then you agree that Disruptive Advertising may share all data it obtains from you, including product performance data, with our Promotional Partner, and our Promotional Partner shall have the same rights to access and use said data as Disruptive Advertising itself.

5\. Use and Protection of Personal Information  
Disruptive Advertising will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. However, we may transfer personal information in connection with a sale or merger of Disruptive Advertising or the division responsible for the services provided to you. We may also share your personal information, such as your email address, mailing address, etc., with our technical consultants, third party auditors, and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality, or provide associated services, and/or who deal with you in processing your orders and/or delivering content, samples, products, services, gifts, and prizes. These third parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purposes of providing the applicable services. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. Our site and services are maintained in the United States of America. By using the site and/or services, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

6\. Other Information We Collect and Use  
We may collect non-personally identifiable information with cookies, such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. This aggregate information is analyzed and combined with similar aggregate information of other users and may be collected both on our site and on other sites in our Advertising Service. We may share aggregate information with our business partners and other third parties. Such aggregate information is anonymous and does not identify any individual user, and we do not link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information. We use proprietary Otracking.com persistent cookies and adhere to a strict P3P tracking policy (for more information, visit http://otracking.com/w3c/policy.html). You can remove persistent cookies by following directions on your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites, and to tailor our product and service offerings to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

7\. Data Retention  
All personally identifiable information that we collect from you is retained for a period of time after our relationship with you ends. This is true whether you only explored obtaining services from us and either rejected or did not accept an offer to provide services, whether you obtained services from us and later terminated those services, or whether you obtained services from us and the term of those services was fulfilled. In each case, we will retain all personally identifiable information for a period of two (2) years following the end of our relationship with you, or from the date that you rejected an offer of services, or from the date that an offer of services lapsed (whichever is later).  
During the period of data retention described above, all personally identifiable information will be retained and kept secure in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.  
At any time during the period of data retention described above, you may elect to have your personally identifiable information deleted from our databases by emailing support@DisruptiveAdvertising.com. In any such email, please include your name, email address, phone number, physical address, business name, and domain with “Remove Personally Identifiable Information” in the subject line, so that we can properly identify you and process your opt-out request. Please note that a reasonable period of time will be required to process your request after Disruptive Advertising receives it.  
Please be aware that non-personally identifiable information that you provide or that we gather may not be subject to this data retention period, and you cannot elect to have it deleted, especially in the event that such non-personally identifiable information is aggregated with other such information in an attempt to improve our services or understand our customer base, or other legitimate purposes under this Privacy Policy. Rest assured that in any such event, all such information is anonymous and will be handled as set forth in the previous section entitled “Other Information We Collect and Use.”

8\. Third Party Website Links  
Some of our websites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our affiliates, business partners, and advertisers. We have no access to or control over their practices. Because Disruptive Advertising does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties’ websites, you should review their respective privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personal information.

9\. Security Information  
Disruptive Advertising stores all data using industry-standard security devices, such as firewalls and encryption protocols, to prevent unauthorized access to our data. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol which provides encryption during transmission.  
We have put in place policies to restrict access to your information by our employees. Our employees are trained to safeguard your information. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

10\. Protection for Children  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.

11\. Changes to This Privacy Policy  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes to this privacy statement on www.DisruptiveAdvertising.com and other places we deem appropriate, so you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes.

12\. Effective Date  
This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on January 22, 2013.  
Disruptive Advertising, Inc.  
support@disruptiveadvertising.com  
1715 East 130 North Spanish Fork, UT, 84660  
1-877-956-7510
